and today i'm going to react to
funny programming hacking scenes on
movies from
all around the world let's get started
oh that's wolverine
all right
oh my god here we go 3d again
it's a cube please confirm what
you can say wait assembling ports scan
objects
they love these 3d stuff and movies i
think it's because the actual console
thing looks really
boring
oh no he loves one cube oh no he looks
too cute
[Music]
oh i think this is more fun than my
actual job
i wish it was true i would love to hack
into 3d
3d cubes but this makes it makes
programming
[Music]
it's like he's dancing with the
communication ah he's standing up
oh here we go the 3d again assembly
assembling crypto algorithm and the
program he's running on is called
warm generator 2. oh this is brilliant
you see this makes me want to learn how
to program
look at that how many screens has got
one two three four five
six oh this is awesome
oh yeah i i hope people think that
programmers do that that's brilliant
there you go you did all the cubes oh my
god the cubes together
oh good job wolverine brilliant job
oh this is amazing okay so mr robot is
pretty accurate though i used to watch
it and it's all right yeah
yeah like they really put effort on
oh here we go ubuntu okay
maybe he's doing his upgrading packages
there we go
password for caretaker he went yeah you
go ubuntu
he login as a caretaker he go to the
temporary directory
it's pretty accurate this oh here we go
you see this is how it looks like
boring just texture that is not really
going on step two
build mouth slowly yeah
there is no dancing that is not drinking
ah dude i love mr robert goddard you're
so good the feeling never gets old
fdp in one hour he says that to his
friends
on the chat [ __ ] yes you are the best
yes you are mr robert you are the best
oh bon anime
what is this what is it what is this
what is this what is it
so holy [ __ ] nobody can do this
this is so fast there is pop-ups
everybody's obsessed with pop-ups
people don't have we don't use pop-ups
so much we have one console one
this is brilliant
[Music]
yes
what is this oh i'm loving this so much
ah
here we go system bridge right sink drop
that's a thing it's not a rat it's like
it's a thing
it's a thing it's a thinker sync to the
main server
firewall one two three four they have
five firewalls
wait they're seeing live progress and
somebody hacking their firewall remote
look at that [ __ ] he's got five
firewalls
he's got five firewalls and he can see
live progress
of when he's been outer layer of our
system
i'll start an intrusion inspection he's
going to start an
intrusion oh my god here we go with the
3d going on
look at this oh no wait i play address
is being
oh my god the lyrium people know oh
can you stop him no i want to watch this
movie i can't slow him down
oh i can't slow him down there is always
a clueless person
next to the hacker he's like oh my god
they are killing us can you stop them
oh no they got a map
start counter strike
this is awesome let's go oh no this is
amazing
three miles look look at this oh no
there's a cat
oh it's a ha it's a it's a cat virus
[Music]
what is this that could actually happen
you could open a lot of things at the
same time like
videos it doesn't seem like locks at
what happened with the i want to see the
map again that barely slowed him down
i'm sorry but he's going to find us in
less than a minute should we abort
no oh he's trying to slow him down by
showing him cuts blinky boxes
here we go hack located
okay
okay let's go let's go with the hack the
cryptid oh my god this is awesome there
is a progress
oh no i could launch a cyber nuke i can
launch
a cyber nuke did he just say that he
just said i can launch
a cybernetic completely frightened oh my
god he's a nuke
no
it's a real nuke it's a missile
he has a missile on his screen
he's got a backup system at home is that
a go for launch is that i go for launch
oh my god he's gonna launch the nuke
oh my god look at how they go
[Music]
the nuke just hit you just
there you go i'm afraid armageddon just
happened
oh that was amazing he has a nuke
oh he has a counter strike oh my god
that's brilliant
okay are they going to the telephone
cables
oh [ __ ] they have access to the is that
the internet
wait this is pretty they are copying a
file
no system you save that mp4
okay weak update
okay they look in the directory
this is actually not bad there is no 3d
you see there is no cubes going on
oh look at that they are oh wow they had
the whole exchange
look at that look at everybody looking
at one person that's amazing
the attention they get he doesn't look
like a
like a kebab shower already he's a fancy
kid oh my god there is a button that
says attack
but he's just pinging he
he just blinked to an ip address that's
oh my god destroy this system
wow look at that window such power
destroyed he's thinking about it destroy
the system
maybe oh my god i want i need to finish
we need to finish this movie i really
want to see what happens
oh my god you're thank you so much for
watching
this has been very fun very interesting
let me know on the comments
uh which one was your favorite one i
don't know all of them are so cool
people dancing
mr robot is the most accurate one i i
really like the missile
thank you for watching let me know what
you think in the comments again if you
have any other
scenes or movies i should react to let
me know please i want to do this again
and as always don't forget to be happy
don't forget to eat kimchi kamidaro
bye-bye